PARISARA ASSAWAPREECHAANAN

+668-9953-0739



p.assawapreechaanan@gmail.com



parisara1992.github.io



PROFILE

Flight attendant from Japan Airlines. Possesses unique leadership and coordination experiences from safety and time critical as an airline personnel, detail oriented and very determined to achieve the goal. Study coding and Full-stack development in free time.

Now I am pursuing software/tech career due to my own passion and love in writing clean code and develop software product that satisfying user experience. Naturally inquisitive and high ambition in self development, love to learn and improve in everyday basis.

EDUCATION

Thammasat University

Software Engineer

Bachelor of Law 2010 - 2014

Relevant Coursework: Introduction to Law and Legal System, Civil Law, Criminal Law, Public and Private International Law.

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Java, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS
- Frameworks: Express, Node.js, AngularJS, React.js, Bootstrap, JQuery, Cucumber
- Databases: SQL, Postgres, DB2, MangoDB
- · Tools: Git and Unix
- Data Analytics
- Proficient in Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)

LANGUAGES

English: TOEIC 910Japanese: JLPT N2Korean: TOPIK LEVEL 3

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Flight Attendant

Japan Airlines Co., Ltd. | 2017 - Present

- Maintained and delivered the service in line with the organization's culture and problem-solving abilities, as well as communication skills and service mind.
- Handled each challenging passenger's requirements in a professional and diplomatic method.
- Working and interacting routinely with people of many nationalities around the world.
- · Performing safety checks during flight.
- Guided for safety and comfort to passengers under all aviation rules and regulations of Japan Airlines.

Japanese Interpreter

Yamashita Tech (Thailand) Co., Ltd. | 2015 - 2017

- Communicating and interpreting between Japanese and Thai.
- · Coordinating and supporting Thai's technician.
- Compile and translate manuals and other standardized materials, among other office support.
- Supported sprint planning and execution of team engagement
- initiatives from start to finish, resulting in increased engagement rates on internal communication.